https://www.intellial.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyPrivacy is a fundamental right of every individual. We, at Intellial Solutions, are committed to protecting the security and privacy of our visitors. Intellial Solutions do not spam, sell, rent, or give away the information to any third party/parties.Please ensure that by visiting www.intellial.com, you are agreeing and accepting the policies that are described in this Privacy Policy.This Privacy Policy explains how we use your personal information and data that you provide to us.Information We CollectPersonal InformationThe personal information that we may collect includes name, contact information, IP addresses and other information, identifying you. We may also collect personal information from you at different points, including but not limited to the following:At the time of communicating with you as a prospective customer;When you prefer to visit our website;While registering you as an end-user of our services;When you fill our “Contact Us” form to get in touch with us;Non-personal InformationWe may also collect non-personal data about users whenever they prefer to interact with our website. Non-personal information includes the browser name that user access, the type of device, technical information like operating system and Internet service providers and other similar information via Google Analytics.CookiesOur website does not collect any information about users, except for the information contained in Cookies. Cookies are small text files, which store and retrieve information about your visit to our website. We use cookies to give personalized experienced on our website. Here, you can find how we use cookies:Session cookies: Session cookies are cached for the duration of your use of our website;Permanent cookies: Permanent cookies are stored in your terminal device for the time specified in the Cookie files parameters or until you delete.You can adjust the settings on your computer in order to decline any cookies if you wish to.Disclosing Your InformationWe ensure you that we will not disclose your personal information to any other party than in agreement with this Privacy Policy. Some of the circumstances given below when we may need to share your information:In any situation, when we might have to sell any or all our business to the buyer. We may disclose your personal information when it is legally required by the law, to protect fraud and reduce the risk of fraud.Intellial Solutions never sell, trade or rent users’ personal information to others. If required, we may share general demographic information that is not linked to any personal information regarding visitors with our trusted business partners, affiliates and advertisers for the purpose mentioned above.How We Use Collected Information?Intellial Solutions collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our website.To improve our SiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.SecurityWe make sure that your shared personal or non-personal information is safe and secure from any unauthorized access, use, loss or destruction. Personal or non-personal information provided by you is stored on a safe and secured web server that is managed by Intellial Solutions.Third Party Links/WebsitesIntellial Solutions may link to third-party websites and services when required; however, we are not responsible for privacy statements or the contents of such third-party sites.Changes to Privacy PolicyIntellial Solutions reserves the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time without any prior notice. When we change, edit or remove any part from this privacy policy, we will mention the updated date at the bottom of this privacy policy page. We encourage our users to keep reviewing this page frequently in order to stay updated with the changes that we perform. The continuing use of our website means that you agree and accept those changes.Contact UsIn case, if you have any query or question regarding our Privacy Policy, you can get in touch with us at https://www.intellial.com/contact-us/Contact Address:A-903 (9th Floor), Empire Business Hub, Science city road, Sola, Ahmedabad – 380060, India.Mobile: +91 760000 1306 Landline: +91 (079) 4898 1173 Email: info@intellial.comLATEST POSTSQuality Control with Integrated Inspections in WorkflowAugust 6, 2020 - 10:44 AM5 Most important features of ERP for Electronics ManufacturingApril 22, 2020 - 4:23 PMAssembly Manufacturing Calendar PlanningApril 13, 2020 - 6:00 PMHow to create Bill of Materials for Electronics AssemblyJanuary 25, 2020 - 5:26 PMLegalTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyCookie PolicyGDPR ComplianceQUICK LINKSAbout usSparrow ERP Electronics & High Tech ManufacturingElectronics Manufacturing Services (EMS)Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)Trading – B2B/B2CSparrow ERP Video CollectionCarecoll Help Desk & Live ChatCONTACTEmail:info@intellial.comPhone:+91 760000 1306Business Hours:10AM to 7PM India Time.ERP for B2B
TradingERP for
Discrete ManufacturingERP for Process
ManufacturingERP for
Electronics AssemblyERP for PCB
ManufacturingERP for e-Commerce BusinessCRM SoftwareSales & Marketing
